

### **EDUCATION**

# MA / Intercultural Anglophone Studies

University of Bayreuth, Germany 2017

# MA / English Language and Literature

Fu Jen Catholic University, Taiwan 2017

# BA / History

Fu Jen Catholic University, Taiwan 2012

### **KEY SKILLS**

### Languages

Chinese (native), English (fluent)

Leading and Organizational Skills on Class and Team-Size Basis

Ability to Provide Constructive Suggestions and Problem-Shooting Solutions

Communication and Presentation Skills

# Jenny Jingyi Li

# Lecturer

#### **ABOUT ME**

Hi, my name is Jenny Li. I am lecturer with 7 years of coaching experience in English language: one-on-one essay writing, online teaching, *English In Use* workshops, and a series of English self-learning courses. I am primarily experienced in coaching presentation skills and English conversation, and designing courses through integrating games that could effectively increase learning motivation.

Meanwhile, I also have considerable experience in teaching English writing techniques including basic/advance grammar and essay structure.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### LECTURER

Dept. of English Language and Literature / FJU / 2018-present

Instructed *Junior Conversation* and advised 13 junior students

Designed a series of online English self-learning courses and intermittently offered *English In Use* workshop sessions

One-on-one coached college students in English writing, offered constructive suggestions for further essay revision

#### ONLINE ENGLISH TUTOR

Association for the Advancement of Online Tutoring / Taiwan / 2017-present

Composed game-based teaching materials and remotely taught children English vocabulary and phonics online

Ability to Signal Potential Problems or Obstacles Working in an International Environment **HOBBIES** 

Course content and material interface optimization

Reading novels

Listening to rock / indie music

Playing Steam games and **MMORPGs** 

## **CONTACT / SOCIAL**

Jenny Li FB

+886911158420 **图** 

jenny50831@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in /jennyjingyi-li/

#### **EXPERIENCE CONTINUED**

#### INTERN

Association for the Advancement of Online Tutoring / Taiwan / 2015

Produced online teaching materials and remotely taught children English phonics and vocabulary online

#### LIBRARY WRITING TUTOR

Fu Jen Catholic University Library / Taiwan / 2013-2015

> Guided college students to understand basic/advanced knowledge of English grammar, composition, as well as writing techniques

One-to-one coached students in essay-writing, offered constructive revising suggestions

#### **ENGLISH TEACHER**

HESS International Educational Group / Taiwan / 2012

> Taught English grammar, phonics, and vocabulary to primarily elementary school students

Communicated students' affairs with parents, provided solutions for individuals learning issues and obstacles

Occasionally supported classroom holiday events and activities

#### REFERENCES

References are available upon request.